[Please tell me if I did anything wrong.]
But no matter what happens,
I hope your friend
can speak his mind.
You drank yesterday.
No matter how much I drank,
I couldn't get back what I lost.
You go rest over there.
I'll handle it.
Junjia.
She...
She was taken by someone else.
Didn't you say you wanted
to observe for a while longer?
Yeah.
I observed for a week,
and finally she got together
with someone else.
One week?
You haven't even expressed your love yet,
right?
What are you crying for?
You know nothing.
A week's observation still means love.
I stayed with her every day,
buying her breakfast,
carrying her things,
and telling her all the jokes I know.
But finally, she just said,
"The person I like expressed
his love to me."
Then I had nothing.
But
you had known she liked someone else.
Why did you still like her?
Liking her is my business.
What does it have to do with her?
I'm fine even though I was rejected.
I really regret
not telling her my feelings.
Welcome...
Wei, help me out.
Excuse me.
Do you have
another part-timer here?
Could I know where he is?
You mean Junjia?
He...
He got off work early today.
Thanks.
I bought you a new strap.
Change it if you want.
Jiayi.
Are you okay?
What's up?
You still care about me after all.
Let go.
I said I would never let you go again.
Senior.
I won't let you go again.
No matter what happens,
I will always find you
in the midst of the crowds.
Jiayi.
It's okay.
But why did you let me go?
I'm sorry.
As long as you don't let me go,
I won't let you go either.
Tell me.
What did I do wrong?
You did nothing wrong.
Then why are you avoiding me?
Because I fell for you.
[Smile After Tears]
[Sixth fret: Love never plays
by the rules]
Because I fell for you.
Just for a moment.
Give me some time.
I will definitely give you
the answer you want.
Judging from recent conditions,
I found the tumor is much more stable.
As long as you keep
taking your medicine on time
and staying happy,
there's no need to worry too much.
It's the first time
I've seen you so happy.
Really?
Otherwise, when would you
go out of your way to text your dad?
How could you peek at my phone?
Did you meet someone?
Now, you
are just like your dad.
You've become very gentle.
He used to be cool
and reserved.
It wasn't until he met me
that I realized
he was a very gentle person.
Only then did I understand
that love can change a person.
But, Mom,
do I really have
the right to love someone right now?
Why do you have to ask yourself
if you have the right to love someone?
Life is short.
Now that time is limited,
there is more reason to love.
[Jiayi]
Regret
is often not about
loving the wrong person,
but about never having loved at all.
[Guitar Friends]
Long time no see.
Here to restock?
We have new fretboard oil
on the left shelf.
Take a look yourself.
I want to buy a guitar today.
We just got two new models.
Come on, let me show you.
Do you have the kind
with a clean tone
and an HSS configuration?
Try this one.
Its pickup configuration is standard.
It feels a bit stiff,
but the sustain is quite stable.
This one feels a bit stiff.
I hope its overtone layers
can perform a bit better.
And
I hope it's durable.
Okay.
Then, try this one.
Its resonance is more delicate,
and the grip feels more solid.
But it's more expensive.
I rarely see students
choose a guitar at this level.
Are you giving it to someone?
This one.
Okay.
We have a free engraving service.
Do you need it?
Yes.
Here,
write down what you want to engrave.
Seems like he is a very important person
to you.
Cherish this bond.
That's okay.
Thanks.
[Senior He]
Hello.
Are you free this weekend?
Yeah.
What's up?
I want to talk to you about something
about the two of us.
Okay.
Senior.
Did you notice?
We didn't hit any red lights today.
Today
must be a lucky day.
[Xpark Aquarium]
I've bought tickets.
Let's go.
I can't remember the last time
I went to the aquarium.
I'm so looking forward to it.
Then, today,
I'll make up for all your happiness.
Let's go.
Penguins.
Look,
so cute.
Pretty, right?
Senior He,
don't you think it's weird?
Fish have a memory of only seven seconds.
They live in the same space
and clearly know each other,
yet act like strangers.
Like acquaintances but also strangers.
My family used to keep fish.
One male fish
would mate with many female fish.
Although I saw many baby fish born,
I always felt
fish are the scummiest creatures,
forgetting the ones they once loved.
Some animals are just born to reproduce.
You can't call them scummy.
I know.
But I have a question.
Is love
really only worth seven seconds?
I once read a book
that said,
"loving only once in a lifetime
is happiness".
Some animals also love only once,
like the penguins we just saw.
They love only once in a lifetime.
So do some fish.
Like the French angelfish.
They live,
travel,
and even hunt in pairs.
I think
true love
is not seven seconds,
nor a lifetime,
but every moment you spend with someone.
Just like now.
[Heartbeats and Underwater Shadows]
What are you doing?
You'll fall in a second.
No, I won't.
What?
Nothing.
Careful.
See?
I told you you'd fall.
With you holding me,
I won't fall.
Okay.
What do you mean?
Wait for me here.
I'll be right back.
So mysterious.
[Alarm clock]
[Good night.] [Good morning.]
Let's review electromagnetic waves.
A magnetic field that changes over time
generates an electric field.
So, under mutual induction,
a regularly changing electric field
is generated in space.
[Electromagnetic in a vacuum]
After we got together,
life went on.
I still studied hard.
Maybe it is
because you're in your senior year
that club activities are suspended
for a few days.
I still have to work part-time
every night.
Junjia.
Go back and rest.
I'll go back after I finish cleaning up.
I prepared this for you.
Your favorite.
Take it back and eat.
Just take it.
Hurry up and rest.
Here,
we two will clean up.
And let me tell you,
Wei is in love again.
I will always remember
that smile of love.
It was just like
the first touch of hands.
And the first time you worried about me
when I first met you.
If it hurts,
why didn't you tell me?
The first time you held my hand.
The first time
you embraced me.
It's fine.
And
the first time you turned around.
Thanks.
He Yankai.
Didn't you say
true love
is not seven seconds,
nor a lifetime,
but every moment you spend with someone?
But
you were the short seven seconds
after turning around and letting me go.
[Preview of the Next Episode]
In terms of many things,
we don't have a second chance.
Are you
Jiayi?
Do you know
you're very happy?
Where is this?